Guide to the Citizen Soldier records, 1966-2007
Citizen Soldier records, 1966-2007
- Series I. Incoming and chronological correspondence
  - 1992
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - May-Jun. (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Jul.-Aug. (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Sept.-Oct. (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - 1993
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - January (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Feb. (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Mar. (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Apr. (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - May-June (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Jul.-Aug (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - Sept.-Oct. (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Mar.-May (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Jun.-Jul. (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Aug.-Oct. (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 1994
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - May-July (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Aug.-Sept. (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Oct.-Nov. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Mar.-May (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - June-July (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Aug.-Nov. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - 1995
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - May-June-July (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Aug.-Sept. (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Oct.-Nov. (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb.-Mar.-Apr. (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - May-June-July (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Aug.-Sept.-Oct. (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - 1996
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Mar.-April (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Apr.-May (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - May-June (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - July-Aug.-Sept. (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Sept.-Oct.-Nov. (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - May-June-July (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - Aug.-Sept.-Oct. (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - 1997
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb.-Mar. (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - Apr.-May (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - June-July (Box 24, Folder 38)
      - Aug.-Sept. (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - Oct.-Nov.-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 24, Folder 41)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Box 24, Folder 42)
      - May-June-July (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - Aug.-Sept. (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Oct.-Nov.-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 45)
      - Jan.-Feb.-Mar. 1998 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Apr.-May-June 1998 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - July-Aug.-Sept. 1998 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Oct.-Nov.-Dec. 1998 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Jan.-Feb.-Mar. 1999 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Apr.-May-June 1999 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - July-Aug.-Sept. 1999 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Oct.-Nov.-Dec. 1999 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - 1998
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. Mar. (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Apr.-May (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - June-July-Aug. (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Sept.-Oct.-Nov. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb.-Mar. (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Apr.-May-June (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - July-Aug.-Sept. (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Oct.-Nov.-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - 1999
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Apr.-May-June (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Aug.-Sept.-Oct.-Nov. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb.-Mar. (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Apr.-May-June (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - July-Aug.-Sept. (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Oct.-Nov.-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - 2000
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb.-Mar.-April (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb.-Mar.-April (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - May-June-July-Aug. (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Sept.-Oct.-Nov.-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - 2001
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb.-March (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Apr.-May-June (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - July-Aug.-Sept.-0ct. (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - 2002
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Feb.-Mar.-April (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - May-June-July (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Aug.-Sept.-Oct. (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - 2003
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Feb.-Mar.-Apr. (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - May-June-July (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Aug.-Sept. (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Oct.-Nov.-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Feb.-Mar.-Apr. (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - May-June-July (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Aug.-Sept. (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Oct.-Nov.-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - 2004
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb.-Mar. (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - Apr.-May-June (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - July-Aug.-Sept. (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - Oct.-Nov.-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - 2014
    - E-mails regarding the death of Tod Ensign (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Series II. Organization/Date: Citizens' Commission of Inquiry on U.S. War Crimes, 1970-1971
  - War Crimes
    - Clippings, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Peace groups, publications, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Vets for Peace, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Commissions, documentation, data, etc., 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Reprinted news articles for handouts, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, Con Son Prison story, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, Herrod, Duffy cases, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, Calley case, correspondence, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, Son-My defendents, others, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, Jan.-Mar., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Clippings, Apr.-June, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, July-Oct., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, Nov.-Dec., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - UPI, news story, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - National Inquiry, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Commissions, proposals, statements, etc., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Commissions, GI vets, AGCS, Johnson letter, Spock letter, report, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Commissions, Springfield, MA, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Commissions of Inquiry Coordinating Committee, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Commissions, press statements, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Commissions, publications and records, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Citizens' Commission, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Winter Soldier Investigation (drafts), 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Mark Lane (clippings), 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - "Dear Friend" letters, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Jane Fonda, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Handouts and reports, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - News clippings and handouts, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Stockholm Conference, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Education/Action Conference, ca. 1970 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Letters to editor on atrocities (from civilians), ca. 1970 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Photographs, slides, negatives printed, ca. 1970 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Handouts (reprints of news clippings), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Clippings, Jan.-Mar., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Clippings, Apr.-June, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - War crimes leads (clippings), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Index to proposal for Congressional hearings, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Gen. Donaldson, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Tony Herbert (Col.), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Calley case, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - WSI news coverage, ca. 1971 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Indochina Chronicle, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - The Rand Vietnam interview series, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - V.V.A.W., 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 46-48)
    - Columbia Journalism Review, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Testimonies, resumes, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - CCI, Winter Soldier, 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - CCI, War Crimes, 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Citizen's Commision, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Racism
    - Witnesses, military hearings, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Dellums, military hearings, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Black Caucus, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Black Caucus, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Dellums, miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Paper by Edward Sowders, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous, various dates (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Magazine articles, various dates (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Series III. Organization/Date: Safe Return Amnesty Committee, 1971-1975
  - Amnesty
    - GI and draft resistance publications, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 62-64)
    - "Tim", 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Press release, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 66-68)
    - Draft proposal, open letter to President Nixon, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Abzug Bill, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - F.B.I., 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - American Exile Newsletter, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - American Exile Newsletter, 1973 (Box 8, Folder X)
    - American Exile Newsletter, 1974 (Box 8, Folder X)
    - Amex/Canada, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Amnesty, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
    - Amnesty, General, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
    - Amnesty, General (clippings), 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Amnesty, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
    - Amnesty (clippings), 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Amnesty publicity, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Amnesty publicity (clippings), 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Amnesty, GI's (clippings), 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Amnesty, GI's (clippings), 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - John Herndon, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 14-15)
    - John Herndon (clippings), 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - CCCO Newsletter (Discharge), 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 17-19)
    - Handouts of news clippings, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Political statements, correspondence, and press releases, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
    - Kennedy hearings, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Clippings, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Statistics, figures, etc. (clippings), 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 25-27)
    - Statistics, figures, etc., 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Discharges, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 29-30)
    - Reports, papers, etc., 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 31-32)
    - Miscellaneous amnesty photos, handouts, reports, etc., 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 33-34)
    - Thomas Michaud case (see also Box 18), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 35-36)
    - Handouts, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Clippings, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 38-39)
    - Transcript of proceedings: family testimony on amnesty, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Transcript of proceedings: the effects of less-than-honorable discharges of Vietnam-era veterans, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Miscillaneous Documents, inc. UP FROM EXILE, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - NUUAC, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - F.O.R.A., 1973 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Campaign for Amnesty, ca. 1973 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Veterans National Resource Project (NCC, Jack Smith), ca. 1973 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Display "Ad", 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 47-48)
    - 'Spin' code story, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 49-50)
    - Richard Bucklin case, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - L. Simon and Ed McNally case, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 52-53)
    - Handouts, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Amnesty miscellaneous (see also Box 17), 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Publicity, articles, etc. Safe Return Amnesty Committee, predecessor, Citizen Soldier (Vietnam Resisters) Amnesty Strugglee (see also Box 17), 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Clippings, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Amnesty publicity, clippings, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 2-5)
    - Amnesty publicity, photocopied clippings, notes, etc., 1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Publications, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Amnesty International, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Clemency Information Center, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
    - Clemency Information Center Indiana Polls, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - LARAS proposal, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Amnesty, Carter, Ford, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Amnesty, Carter, Ford clippings, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 14-16)
    - First National Convention, Amnesty International, U.S.A., June 1, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Christmas cards and bracelets, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 18-19)
    - Andrew A. Brakke, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Campaign 1974, response from candidates, ca. 1974 (Box 10, Folder 21-25)
    - Amnesty publications, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - P.S.A. Network contacts, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - P.S.A. contact, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - NCUUA, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Campaign 100 (Research), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 30-32)
    - Reports, press releases, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Amnesty legislation (94th Congress), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Amnesty (General), 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Performing Artists Lobby (April 7th), 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Clippings, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Candidates' statements on amnesty, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 38-39)
    - Congressional interview forms, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - NCUUA, current materials, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Public Advertising Council, ca. 1976 (Box 10, Folder 42-43)
    - Amnesty, general, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Amnesty, clippings, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Amnesty, clippings and handouts, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Toronto Amnesty Conference, Jan. 29, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Amnesty, miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Discharge upgrading, re: Carter's pardon, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Balaban film project, ca. 1977 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Handouts, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - L. Font, Coast Guard case, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Handouts and clippings (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Agendas, proposals, and drafts of papers (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Movie treatment, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Sample of mail or comments hostile to amnesty, various dates (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Amnesty report, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Clippings (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - FORA brochure (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Discharges II, desertion stats, etc. (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Political Issues
    - Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - "Air War", 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Diem, assassination, Hillsman memo, and related clippings, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Youth voters, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Berkeley, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - War protest, ca. 1971 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - People's Party, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Harrisburg-8, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - NACLA Handbook, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Defense Monitor, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - C.A.R.I.C., 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Public International Communications, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Center for Defense Information, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - RECON, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - ROTC/JROTC recruitment, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - National Association of Concerned Vets, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - VOLAR, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Advertisements, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - In the Public Interest, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Decolonization Committee, Puerto Rico, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Environmental Action, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Informer file, ca. 1974 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Army Times II, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Aliyah, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - American Committee on Africa, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Mid-East Project, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Coalition for New Foreign Policy, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - The Progressive, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Clippings and handouts, various dates (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Portugal
    - Portugal Information Center, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 30-31)
    - Portugal Information Center (with photos), 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Portugal Information Center, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 33-34)
    - Portugal (general), 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Portugal Information Center, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 36-38)
    - APOIO Newsletter, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Portugal clippings, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Portugal Information Center (general), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Portugal, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Series IV. Organization/Date: Citizen Soldier, 1966-2007
  - Unions
    - RESIST, and other union material, 1968-1974 (Box 11, Folder 43-45)
    - NPAC, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - People's Peace Treaty, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Center for National Security Studies, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 48-49)
    - American Veterans Movement, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Workers' Defense League, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Seed Fund (proposal), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Unionization, military, press clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Unionization, military, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - American Federation of Government Employees, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Institute of Industrial Relations, University of Calfornia at Los Angeles, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Article on military unionization, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Report to American Federation of Government Employees, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - FORWARD, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Unionization issue, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Safe Return's contacts with GI support groups & unions in Europe, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Military unions (articles), 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    - Letters from GI's re: unionization, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - Military (general), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Military organization (paper), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Military unionization, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - GIPA News and Discussion Bulletin, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 8-10)
    - Military unions, notes on interviews, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 11-12)
    - Handouts, clippings, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Army on Strike!, by M. Uhl and T. Ensign, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Senior Conference, participants and proceedings, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Handouts, pamphlets, etc., 1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - AFGE, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Association of Civilian Technicians, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous reports on unions, various dates (Box 12, Folder 19-21)
    - Appalachian Movement, various dates (Box 12, Folder 22-23)
  - Health Issues
    - Medical Commission for Human Rights, 1966-1974 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Army, nerve gas defoliation, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Army, drugs, 1971, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Post-Vietnam syndrome, 1974, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Clippings, ca. 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Papers, reports, data, ca. 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - WIN, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Curriculum vitae, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 31-32)
    - C.A.S.T., 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Clippings, 1979, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Agent Orange, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - VA memos/circulars, ca. 1979 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, various dates (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Handouts, general information, various dates (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - National Toxicology Program Report on a,4-D, a,4,5-T, and TCDD (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Prison/P.O.W. Issues
    - P.O.W., 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Military Practices Review Board (proposal), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - SCER (vets, military subjects), 1972 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Families of victims (clippings), 1972 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Political Education Project (Boston), 1973 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - P.O.W.'s (anti-war), 1973 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - David Remme, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Penthouse series "Vietnam Vets", 1974 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous P.O.W. and prison information, various dates (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Organizational Files
    - Letters to the editor, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Commissions, general correspondence, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Annapolis, Baltimore commissions, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 51-52)
    - Personal fldr., M. Uhl, various dates (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Disability cases, M. Uhl, various dates (Box 12, Folder 54-55)
    - Fund-raising (ideas), various dates (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Fund-appeal letters, various dates (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Stationery ideas, various dates (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Organizational calendar, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Foundation material, various dates (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Mailing problems, etc. U.S. Post, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Vietnamese propaganda leaflets (Chieu Hoi) (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Citizen Soldier (newsletter), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - "Atomic Vets" testimony, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Book - "Guinea Pigs: American Veterans and the Abuse of Power", 1977 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Brannon, Mrs. Vivian, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - JABARA, Freedom of Information Act, ca. 1975 (Box 13)
  - Agent Orange, (Other Agent Orange material in Box 12)
    - Agent Orange, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Agent Orange miscellany (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Agent Orange publicity (1) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Agent Orange publicity (2) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Benton Musslewhite, Inc. - Agent Orange class action suit (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Summit, Stuart law firm (Agent Orange initiative) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Cooper, Mrs. Margarete (Agent Orange case) (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Green, Willie and Thelma (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Wahl, Bruce (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Monsanto workers, Agent Orange trial, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Bhopal, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Bhopal (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Dapsone (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Publicity re: 1984 settlement (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Class Assistance Foundation (Box 18, Folder 29-30)
    - Musselwhite disbarment, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Agent Orange, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Agent Orange, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Agent Orange Recent Publicity (Dioxin), 1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - D.C. press conference: A.O. lawsuit, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 29-32)
    - Agent Orange Comm., 2002-2004 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Agent Orange work, 1978-1984 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Testing
    - Jaffee, Stanley, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Broudy case (1) (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Broudy case (2) (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - HERO (Hazards of electromagnetic radiation to ordnance), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - HERO lawsuit, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Newberg, Herbert, Atty., 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Piekarski, Timothy, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Toxic Chemicals
    - David, Jack, Jr. (Box 18, Folder 21-23)
  - Drug Testing
    - Drug testing, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Drug testing (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Childs, John (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Drugs - chemical testing (Scientologist material) (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Drugs - chemical testing (Scientologist material) (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - Death/Suicide
    - Lee, Craig (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Heim, John (Box 20, Folder 4-5)
    - LeBarron, Trevor (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Testing
    - Alverez, Carlos (Box 20, Folder 7)